<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<doc xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="..\Documentation\Documentation.xsd">
  <assembly>
    <name>Elysium</name>
  </assembly>
  <members>
    <type name="T:Elysium.AccentBrushes">
      <summary>
        Contains a set of brushes with a solid filling based on one of the accent colours.
      </summary>
    </type>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Blue">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of blue (#FF017BCD).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of blue (#FF017BCD).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Brown">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of brown (#FFA05000).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of brown (#FFA05000).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Green">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of green (#FF339933).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of green (#FF339933).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Lime">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of lime (#FF8CBF26).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of lime (#FF8CBF26).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Magenta">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of magenta (#FFFF0097).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of magenta (#FFFF0097).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Mango">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of mango (#FFF09609).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of mango (#FFF09609).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Orange">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of orange (#FFCB5201).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of orange (#FFCB5201).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Pink">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of pink (#FFE671B8).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of pink (#FFE671B8).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Purple">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of purple (#FF69227B).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of purple (#FF69227B).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Red">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of red (#FFE51400).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of red (#FFE51400).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Rose">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of rose (#FFD80073).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of rose (#FFD80073).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Sky">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of light blue (#FF1BA1E2).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of light blue (#FF1BA1E2).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Viridian">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of viridian (#FF00ABA9).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of viridian (#FF00ABA9).</value>
    </property>
    <property name="P:Elysium.AccentBrushes.Violet">
      <summary>
        Returns a brush with the solid fill colour of violet (#FFA200FF).
      </summary>
      <value>A brush with the solid fill colour of violet (#FFA200FF).</value>
    </property>
  </members>
</doc>